<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Email Clients for Linux</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/email-clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/email-clients/</guid>
      <description>TLDR; Thunderbird is the best email client (sUrpRisE) but Mailspring is quite close if it didn&amp;rsquo;t have some issues.
Context This article is a weird child. Some people do not use email clients because they have just one email for everything and they might use aliases but you are still weird for using one.
I have around 3-4 emails and then I manage other emails too which requires me to have an email client rather than logging in every email at all times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Everyone</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/linux-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/linux-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Linux is an important tool especially for hackers. ethical of course.
From today (26.6.23) I will be posting Linux guides, ranging from linux commands to installing &amp;amp; using hacking tools.
Day 1 pwd in GUI (Graphical User Interface), its easy to know where you are however in terminal it might not be straight forward.
Firstly, you can see above the input area however this doesn&amp;rsquo;t show the full path at times which is why we use the command is pwd which is a shortform for &amp;ldquo;Print Working Directory&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create SSH Keys &amp; Install Them on a Linux System</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/ssh-keys-from-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/ssh-keys-from-linux/</guid>
      <description>Why? Just Use Passwords. SSH key pairs outperform passwords in terms of security and convenience. SSH keys resist brute-force attacks thanks to strong cryptographic algorithms, eliminating the vulnerability of easily guessed or stolen passwords. Key pairs provide convenience by eliminating the need to remember or transmit passwords, lowering human error and increasing security. Furthermore, they improve auditability and accountability. SSH key pairs are a secure authentication method that is both reliable and efficient in systems and applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Get Apple Emojis On Linux</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/apple-emojis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/apple-emojis/</guid>
      <description>Since the last guide on emojis on Linux, some mentioned how some emojis are still missing. I found another font pack on GitHub which works better.
Github: https://github.com/samuelngs/apple-emoji-linux
Download &amp;amp; Install Just download the file from GitHub and either open it and click on install or move the .tiff file to ~/.local/share/fonts
Either way, clear the cache by fc-cache -f -v and reopen your applications or restart your machine and it should work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to Installing Notion on Linux using Epiphany Browser</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/notion-web-app-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/notion-web-app-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Install Debian:
sudo apt update sudo apt install epiphany-browser Fedora:
sudo dnf update sudo dnf install epiphany Arch:
sudo pacman -Syu sudo pacman -S epiphany Flatpak:
sudo flatpak install flathub org.gnome.Epiphany Setup Go to notion.so website in Epiphany Click on the three verticle dots in the upper-right corner Select &amp;ldquo;Install Notion&amp;rdquo; Once the installation is complete, you can launch Notion from your Linux desktop or applications menu.
that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HPLIP Install On Debian</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/hplip-debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/hplip-debian/</guid>
      <description>This guide is written for Hplip installation on Debian 11*
Prerequisites Install the required dependencies by running the following command:
sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt upgrade -y sudo apt install libcups2-dev libssl-dev libusb-1.0-0-dev python3-dev python3-pip Download HPLIP Go to SourceForce and download HPLIP
Once the download is complete, make the file executable by running the following command:
chmod +x hplip-3.16.7.run Note: Replace &amp;ldquo;3.16.7&amp;rdquo; in the above command with the version you downloaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Post-Install Guide</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/fedora-post-install-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/fedora-post-install-guide/</guid>
      <description>Speed up DNF add/edit the following file /etc/dnf/dnf.conf
fastestmirror=True max_parallel_downloads=10 defaultyes=True keepcache=True To clean the cache: dnf clean all
System Update sudo dnf update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo dnf upgrade -y &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo reboot Enable RPM Fusion sudo dnf install https://mirrors.rpmfusion.org/free/fedora/rpmfusion-free-release-$(rpm -E %fedora).noarch.rpm https://mirrors.rpmfusion.org/nonfree/fedora/rpmfusion-nonfree-release-$(rpm -E %fedora).noarch.rpm For any errors or other installation guide, visit rpmfusion.org
Enable Flatpaks flatpak remote-add --if-not-exists flathub https://flathub.org/repo/flathub.flatpakrepo Install Media Codecs sudo dnf groupupdate multimedia --setop=&amp;#34;install_weak_deps=False&amp;#34; --exclude=PackageKit-gstreamer-plugin sudo dnf groupupdate sound-and-video Install GNOME applications Install GNOME Tweaks:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect Your Phone to Linux</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/connect-your-phone-to-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/connect-your-phone-to-linux/</guid>
      <description>Brief Using a extension and an app: IOS &amp;amp; Android and a GNOME extension on Debian based distros.
*I&amp;rsquo;m using Debian 11 and Android 11 for this guide.
Learn more about KDE Connect here: kdeconnect.kde.org
Prerequisites Install the GNOME extension &amp;amp; Install the app from PlayStore
Connect If you are using a firewall like UFW, you have to allow network traffic from port 1716:
sudo ufw allow 1716 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo ufw reload Now make sure both devices are on the same network and then:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must Have GNOME Extensions</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/must-have-gnome-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/must-have-gnome-extensions/</guid>
      <description>The list: Clipboard History Tray Icons AlternateTab ArcMenu Emoji Selector Clipboard History Clipboard Indicator is the most important extension in my opinion, You should now see a clipboard history in the top bar once you install it.
Tray Icons You can enable icons on your top bar
AlternateTab Substitute Alt-Tab with a window based switcher that does not group by application.
ArcMenu Application menu for GNOME Shell
Emoji Selector This extension provides a parametrable popup menu displaying most emojis, clicking on an emoji copies it to the clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Things to Do After Installing Debian</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/things-to-do-after-installing-deb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/things-to-do-after-installing-deb/</guid>
      <description>Enable Dark Mode Search for &amp;ldquo;Tweaks&amp;rdquo; On the left-hand side pane, click on ‘Appearance.’ Next to the applications drop-down menu, select the “Adawaita-dark” option. Add your user to the sudoers file Launch a terminal and follow these commands su - usermod -aG sudo newuser *change your username with &amp;ldquo;newuser&amp;rdquo;
Installing Updates sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt upgrade -y &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo reboot Install a firewall sudo apt install ufw -y Deny all the traffic in and out for now by</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customise Your Prompt with Starship</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/customised-prompt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/customised-prompt/</guid>
      <description>Install curl -sS https://starship.rs/install.sh | sh &amp;amp; add the following to ~/.bashrc
eval &amp;#34;$(starship init bash)&amp;#34; You can also find installation instructions for other operating systems here: https://starship.rs/guide
Config You can now completely customise your prompt by editing the config file, which is accessible via:
starship config alternatively, you can use presets from https://starship.rs/presets/
I prefer Starship&amp;rsquo;s default minimal style, so I don&amp;rsquo;t use any presets or have anything in my config file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Browser Extensions</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/best-browser-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/best-browser-extensions/</guid>
      <description>List Extensity - Quickly enable/disable Google Chrome extensions Cookie Remover - Removes cookies for the current site GoFullPage - Capture a screenshot of your current page in PDF or Image formats INSSIST - Add more functionality to instagram.com Midnigh Lizard - Dark mode on all websites Return YouTube Dislike - Returns ability to see dislikes on YouTube URL Shortener - Free URL shortener Extensity A browser extension that allows you to enable or disable browser extensions with a single click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vital Terminal Tools</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/terminal-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/terminal-commands/</guid>
      <description>TLDR A humane version of man pages.
Install pip3 install tldr AutoJump A faster way to navigate your filesystem. Saves a lot of time.
Install sudo apt install autojump Trash-CLI Deletes the files to recycle bin in terminal.
Install sudo apt install trash-cli You can make a alias for &amp;ldquo;rm&amp;rdquo; to trash-cli by adding the following alias to ~/.bashrc file.
alias rm=&amp;#34;trash&amp;#34; Ccrypt Secure encryption and decryption of files and streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Server on LAN</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/hugo-lan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/hugo-lan/</guid>
      <description>Brief [IP-ADD] is your local IP address.
Command use this command instead of &amp;ldquo;hugo server&amp;rdquo;
hugo server --bind [IP-ADD] --baseURL http://[IP-ADD] Conclusion visit http://[IP-ADD] from any device on your LAN to view the temporary hugo site.
that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UFW | Firewall on Linux Systems</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/linux-firewall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/linux-firewall/</guid>
      <description>Uncomplicated Firewall (UFW) is an easy and beginner friendly firewall for linux systems.
Install sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install ufw Verify Install sudo ufw status Basic Blocks sudo ufw default deny incoming sudo ufw default allow outgoing Enable Firewall sudo ufw enable Blocking Ports you can block any port by &amp;ldquo;sudo ufw deny PORT&amp;rdquo; for example, to block port 76 type:
sudo ufw deny 76 Allow Ports you can allow any port by &amp;ldquo;sudo ufw allow PORT&amp;rdquo; for example, to allow port 22 (default SSH port) type:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better APT</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/better-apt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/better-apt/</guid>
      <description>why not APT? APT has slow mirrors, APT isn&amp;rsquo;t optimised for performance right out of the box, rolling back updates or installs is pain because there is no concept of history and last but not the least, the look of APT is just mehhh.
Nala is just better. Nala fixes all these problems right from the start while having APT is the backend.
Install add repository
echo &amp;#34;deb http://deb.volian.org/volian/ scar main&amp;#34; | sudo tee /etc/apt/sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSL Certificate with Certbot</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/ssl-apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/ssl-apache/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Debian, Apache2, Snapd, Certbot
Install sudo apt update sudo apt install snapd -y install certbot
sudo snap install certbot --classic Create symbolic link so you can run certbot command from the terminal
sudo ln -s /snap/bin/certbot /usr/bin/certbot Run certbot command
sudo certbot --apache you can change &amp;ldquo;&amp;ndash;apache&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;&amp;ndash;nginx&amp;rdquo; if you are using nginx instead of apache
Getting the Cert Enter your valid email address so certbot can contact you for renewal and security notices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Updates on Linux</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/auto-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/auto-updates/</guid>
      <description>Brief Unattendeed Upgrades - Automatic installation of security upgrades on apt based systems.
install sudo apt update sudo apt install unattended-upgrades -y Enable Automatic Updates enable automatic updates by:
sudo dpkg-reconfigure -plow unattended-upgrades &amp;ldquo;-plow&amp;rdquo; is to set prorioty as low for unattended upgrades. select &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo; from these options:
Other config/sources For more about configuration, go through this blog by Hayden James.
that’s it ✌🏽</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View Saved WiFi Passwords</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/saved-Wifi-Pwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/saved-Wifi-Pwd/</guid>
      <description>Brief A way to see WiFi password for linux.
Command cd /etc/NetworkManager/system-connections/ &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo cat [ssid] or use this script
that’s it ✌🏽</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows on Linux</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/windows-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/windows-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Brief Some things just are better on windows than linux thus having a windows virtual machine(VM) is a great idea specially when daily driving linux.
We will be using Vert Manager to use windows 7 on vanilla Debian linux however, this will work on any Debian based system i.e Ubuntu.
Machine I am using: Step 1: Confirm virtualization Open terminal and type
grep -o &amp;#34;vm\|sum&amp;#34; /proc/cpuinfo here the command outputs ‘vmx’ but if u are not using intel processor it will show ‘SVM’ instead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
