<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fix Grub Not Showing for Windows and Linux Dual Boot System</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/no-grub-windows-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/no-grub-windows-linux/</guid>
      <description>Copy-paste the following command:
bcdedit /set {bootmgr} path \EFI\debian\grubx64.efi This is for debian however you can change the folder name for other distributions.
that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Windows Run Quicker</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/make-windows-run-quicker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/make-windows-run-quicker/</guid>
      <description>Windows by default is quite bulky, sum this with a average hardware and now you have a useless blob of metal. You can make the performance better by tweaking several things as explained below.
CTT Wintool Chris Tituss&amp;rsquo; tool is an essential tool to make significant changes to your Windows system. You can run the tool by:
Run Powershell as admin &amp;amp; run: irm christitus.com/win | iex Few tweaks I recommend to make your system run smoother:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Canon Camera as Webcam</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/cannon-camera-as-webcam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/cannon-camera-as-webcam/</guid>
      <description>*Note that the official Canon webcam utility software is only available for Windows and macOS operating systems. Linux users might have to look for third-party solutions or workarounds.
Requirements To use your Canon camera as a webcam, you&amp;rsquo;ll need the following:
A Canon camera that supports the EOS Webcam Utility software, list: https://www.usa.canon.com/cameras/eos-webcam-utility#model A USB cable to connect your camera to your computer The EOS Webcam Utility software (download it from the Canon website) Steps Once you have the requirements ready, follow these steps to use your Canon camera as a webcam:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Install and Use WSL2 on Windows 10: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/wsl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/wsl2/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites You need to enable the WSL feature by:
Open the Start menu and search for &amp;ldquo;Turn Windows features on or off.&amp;rdquo; Scroll down and check the box next to &amp;ldquo;Windows Subsystem for Linux.&amp;rdquo; Click &amp;ldquo;OK&amp;rdquo; and wait for the feature to be installed Install a Linux Distro You can choose between variety of Linux Distributions for WSL however I recommend using Debian as explained here
To install Debian, open CMD or Powershell as admin and run:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Group Policy Back in Windows 10 and 11 with PolicyPlus</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/policy-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/policy-plus/</guid>
      <description>If you need to manage the Group Policy settings in Windows 10 and 11, but find that the Group Policy Editor (gpedit.msc) is not available in your edition of Windows, you can use an open-source application called PolicyPlus instead. Here are the steps to get Group Policy back in Windows 10 and 11 using PolicyPlus:
Download PolicyPlus is available as a .exe file that you can download from the PolicyPlus GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable UAC Prompt Password For Standard User</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/enable-uac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/enable-uac/</guid>
      <description>Simply run this .reg file which will ammend a registery key
the key:
HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE\SOFTWARE\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Policies\System ConsentPromptBehaviorUser DWORD
0 = Automatically deny elevation requests
1 = Prompt for credentials on the secure desktop
3 = Prompt for credentials (default)
that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Utility</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/windows-utility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/windows-utility/</guid>
      <description>Windows is clumsy and sluggish by default, but an application called Windows Utility developed by Chris Titus can considerably improve it.
Usage In PowerShell, run this command as administrator
irm christitus.com/win | iex Simply click on the items you want to change.
Recommendation Select the appropriate option under &amp;ldquo;Tweaks,&amp;rdquo; such as desktop or laptop. Personally, I prefer the &amp;ldquo;Minimal&amp;rdquo; option. Under &amp;ldquo;Updates&amp;rdquo;, select &amp;ldquo;Security Settings&amp;rdquo; that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Update With Powershell</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/windows-update-with-powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/windows-update-with-powershell/</guid>
      <description>*These actions are only possible with administrative privileges.
Prerequisites Install the update module:
Install-Module PSWindowsUpdate Add-WUServiceManager -MicrosoftUpdate Command Install all availble updates
Install-WindowsUpdate -MicrosoftUpdate -AcceptAll -AutoReboot | Out-File &amp;#34;C:\MSUpdates.log&amp;#34; -Force Update logs can be found at: C:\MSUpdates.log
that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Browser Extensions</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/best-browser-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/best-browser-extensions/</guid>
      <description>List Extensity - Quickly enable/disable Google Chrome extensions Cookie Remover - Removes cookies for the current site GoFullPage - Capture a screenshot of your current page in PDF or Image formats INSSIST - Add more functionality to instagram.com Midnigh Lizard - Dark mode on all websites Return YouTube Dislike - Returns ability to see dislikes on YouTube URL Shortener - Free URL shortener Extensity A browser extension that allows you to enable or disable browser extensions with a single click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert Python files to Windows executable files</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/py-to-exe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/py-to-exe/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites You should have all the modules installed before compiling You should have all the requirements for the python file before compiling it Install Nuitka on Windows Go to Go to nuitka.net/download/windows which will download a .msi file
Run the file and click on &amp;ldquo;More info&amp;rdquo;
Click on &amp;ldquo;Run anyway&amp;rdquo;
Click on &amp;ldquo;Install for all users&amp;rdquo; then click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;
Specify the python 3.9 compiler, its easier to use the Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Viruses From Windows</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/remove-viruses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/remove-viruses/</guid>
      <description>Tron is a all in one program to remove any viruses from windows and get windows &amp;ldquo;back on it&amp;rsquo;s feet&amp;rdquo;
Install https://www.reddit.com/r/TronScript/
Reference Chris Titus has a great video on this explaining everything so I will just link it.
that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Debian comepletely from DualBoot</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/remove-dualboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/remove-dualboot/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Windows 10 PC
I - Delete partition Right click on the start button (bottom left corner) and click on &amp;ldquo;Disk Management&amp;rdquo;
ideally there should be 2 linux partition, one swap area and other is main disk partition. These are the two partitions I have
right click on one of them and click on &amp;ldquo;Delete Volume&amp;rdquo;
click yes on the pop up
repeat the last two steps for the second partition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disable Updates</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/disable-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/disable-updates/</guid>
      <description>Brief Windows Update BLocker(Wub) - A minimal tool to block windows updates.
Download You can download the latest version from the official website
Extract the zip file and open the Wub_x64.exe file as adminstator
Here click the second option (Disable updates)
Once you have disabled the updates the app will look like this
You can close the app now.
If you check for updates now in windows settings you will see this error</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
