<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansoorbarri.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Must Have GNOME Extensions</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/must-have-gnome-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/must-have-gnome-extensions/</guid>
      <description>The list:  Clipboard History Tray Icons AlternateTab ArcMenu Emoji Selector  Clipboard History Clipboard Indicator is the most important extension in my opinion, You should now see a clipboard history in the top bar once you install it.
Tray Icons You can enable icons on your top bar
AlternateTab Substitute Alt-Tab with a window based switcher that does not group by application.
ArcMenu Application menu for GNOME Shell
Emoji Selector This extension provides a parametrable popup menu displaying most emojis, clicking on an emoji copies it to the clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Social Media Accounts with Sherlock</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/find-social-media-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/find-social-media-accounts/</guid>
      <description>Brief Hunt down social media accounts by username across social networks with Sherlock
This tool will only work for people who use the same username across all social media platforms.
Installation git clone https://github.com/sherlock-project/sherlock cd sherlock sudo pip3 install -r requirements.txt Find Social Accounts python3 sherlock [username] For example:
python3 sherlock mansoor.yuh you can see other options with -h
usage: sherlock [-h] [--version] [--verbose] [--folderoutput FOLDEROUTPUT] [--output OUTPUT] [--tor] [--unique-tor] [--csv] [--site SITE_NAME] [--proxy PROXY_URL] [--json JSON_FILE] [--timeout TIMEOUT] [--print-all] [--print-found] [--no-color] [--browse] [--local] USERNAMES [USERNAMES .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Things to Do After Installing Debian</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/things-to-do-after-installing-deb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/things-to-do-after-installing-deb/</guid>
      <description>Enable Dark Mode  Search for &amp;ldquo;Tweaks&amp;rdquo; On the left-hand side pane, click on ‘Appearance.’ Next to the applications drop-down menu, select the “Adawaita-dark” option.  Add your user to the sudoers file  Launch a terminal and follow these commands  su - usermod -aG sudo newuser *change your username with &amp;ldquo;newuser&amp;rdquo;
Installing Updates sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo apt upgrade -y &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo reboot Install a firewall sudo apt install ufw -y Deny all the traffic in and out for now by</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customise Your Prompt with Starship</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/customised-prompt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/customised-prompt/</guid>
      <description>Install curl -sS https://starship.rs/install.sh | sh &amp;amp; add the following to ~/.bashrc
eval &amp;#34;$(starship init bash)&amp;#34; You can also find installation instructions for other operating systems here: https://starship.rs/guide
Config You can now completely customise your prompt by editing the config file, which is accessible via:
starship config alternatively, you can use presets from https://starship.rs/presets/
I prefer Starship&amp;rsquo;s default minimal style, so I don&amp;rsquo;t use any presets or have anything in my config file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Browser Extensions</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/best-browser-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/best-browser-extensions/</guid>
      <description>List  Extensity - Quickly enable/disable Google Chrome extensions Cookie Remover - Removes cookies for the current site GoFullPage - Capture a screenshot of your current page in PDF or Image formats INSSIST - Add more functionality to instagram.com Midnigh Lizard - Dark mode on all websites Return YouTube Dislike - Returns ability to see dislikes on YouTube URL Shortener - Free URL shortener  Extensity A browser extension that allows you to enable or disable browser extensions with a single click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Block Websites On Your Home Network</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/home-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/home-security/</guid>
      <description>Brief OpenDNS has a home network security system that you can enable by changing DNS settings on your router&amp;rsquo;s admin page. Because some Internet Service Providers (ISPs), such as Virgin Media, do not allow you to change your DNS, this method may not work for you.
Steps To begin, sign up for OpenDNS, at www.opendns.com/homefree
  Scroll down to enter your information.
  Access your router&amp;rsquo;s administration page; the address is usually printed on the back of the router.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of 2020</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/end-of-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/end-of-2020/</guid>
      <description>Goals for 2022  Posting how-to guides on mansoor.cf everyday  Learning and growing in CyberSecurity   making mansoorbarri.com a IT company  Getting a job  It started off really well at the beginning of this year, but as I got busier, it became a weekly thing, then monthly, and finally a seasonal thing where I would post 5 guides every 2-3 months. However, in the last quarter, I really expanded this into a polished product, which I did not expect at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/aoc4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/aoc4/</guid>
      <description>Room Advent Of Cyber 4
Day 1 | Someone&amp;rsquo;s coming to town! Question 1: Who is the adversary that attacked Santa&amp;rsquo;s network this year? The Bandit Yeti Question 2: What&amp;rsquo;s the flag that they left behind? THM{IT&#39;S A Y3T1 CHR1$TMA$} Day 2 | Santa&amp;rsquo;s Naughty &amp;amp; Nice Log Question 1: Ensure you are connected to the deployable machine in this task. No answer needed
Question 2: Use the ls command to list the files present in the current directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert Python files to Windows executable files</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/py-to-exe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/py-to-exe/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites  You should have all the modules installed before compiling You should have all the requirements for the python file before compiling it  Install Nuitka on Windows   Go to Go to nuitka.net/download/windows which will download a .msi file
  Run the file and click on &amp;ldquo;More info&amp;rdquo;
  Click on &amp;ldquo;Run anyway&amp;rdquo;
  Click on &amp;ldquo;Install for all users&amp;rdquo; then click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;
  Specify the python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FBI Just Got Hacked</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/fbi-hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/fbi-hack/</guid>
      <description>Background As there webstie says, &amp;ldquo;InfraGard is a partnership between the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and members of the private sector for the protection of U.S. Critical Infrastructure. Through seamless collaboration, InfraGard connects owners and operators within critical infrastructure to the FBI, to provide education, information sharing, networking, and workshops on emerging technologies and threats. InfraGard’s membership includes: business executives, entrepreneurs, lawyers, security personnel, military and government officials, IT professionals, academia and state and local law enforcement—all dedicated to contributing industry-specific insight and advancing national security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expose Your Network To The Internet Without Port Forwarding</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/expose-your-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/expose-your-network/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisite This method is entirely free of costs however, you will just need a cloudflare account and a domain which is using Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s nameserver&amp;rsquo;s or is bought with Cloudflare. You can signup with cloudflare on cloudflare.com/signup.
Cloudflare Tunnel is basically a tunnel which works like a VPN, this allows you to expose anything to the internet securely. This can be a website, proxmox server, plex server, docker container or just about anything which requires you to port forward from your router.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Get a Email Verified Badge</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/email-cert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/email-cert/</guid>
      <description>Email Certificates? Yes, these are certificate which verifies that you are using a certain type of encryption (S/MIME) when sending mails. This is rare because it’s not really necessary plus it’s a pain to set it up correctly.
Getting Email Certificate Go to Actalis&#39;s website Enter the email you want to verify, click on “send verification email” and enter the OTP from the email.
*Note: sometimes the email goes to the spam folder so make sure you check that as well</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vital Terminal Tools</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/terminal-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/terminal-commands/</guid>
      <description>TLDR A humane version of man pages.
Install pip3 install tldr AutoJump A faster way to navigate your filesystem. Saves a lot of time.
Install sudo apt install autojump Trash-CLI Deletes the files to recycle bin in terminal.
Install sudo apt install trash-cli You can make a alias for &amp;ldquo;rm&amp;rdquo; to trash-cli by adding the following alias to ~/.bashrc file.
alias rm=&amp;#34;trash&amp;#34; Ccrypt Secure encryption and decryption of files and streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Way To Use GitHub</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/better-gihub/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/better-gihub/</guid>
      <description>Commandline for Github is complicated and complex however a tool called gh makes git so much easier on commandline and makes using Github that much quicker and easy.
Install Debian
sudo apt install gh Windows
winget install -e --id Github.cli Setup gh auth login Follow the prompts but choose SSH as authentication method.
Set your repo to use GH auth git remote set-url origin git@github.com:mansoorbarri/website.git change &amp;ldquo;mansoorbarri/website.git&amp;rdquo; to your repo name*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comments on HUGO site</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/comments-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/comments-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Here I&amp;rsquo;m using Hugo theme called GoKarna but you can pretty much do this with any Hugo theme.
HUGO Setup make a file with the name &amp;ldquo;rawhtml.html&amp;rdquo; in /layours.shortcodes directory of your theme and put the follwing line.
*if your don&amp;rsquo;t have the shortcodes directory, you can make one.
{{.Inner}} Utterances Setup Add utterances to your github repository from github.com/apps/utterances
then get your HTML code from utteranc.es
Add comments Now add the raw html tag followed by your HTML code from utteranc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SideWinder&#39;s attack on Pakistan&#39;s NEPRA</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/nepra-sidewinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/nepra-sidewinder/</guid>
      <description>Background SideWinder is an Indian state-backed Hacker group predominantly known for targetting Pakistan military and other organisations for intel for their own national security. They are also known to target other South &amp;amp; East Asian countries and their institutions like: Nepali Ministry of Defence and Foreign Affairs, Nepali Army, Afghanistan National Security Council &amp;amp; Sri Lankan Defence Ministry.
July 2022 Recently, SideWinder targetted Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s National Electric Power Regulatory Authority (NEPRA) with a personalised malware named WarHawk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirror Android Screen with Sound</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/android-screen-mirror/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/android-screen-mirror/</guid>
      <description>Brief You can&amp;rsquo;t mirror screen and sound together so we&amp;rsquo;ll use two different tools to do the job. This method can be done on Linux &amp;amp; Windows but I am using Linux (Debian) in this case.
Tools Scrcpy - for screen mirror
sndcpy - for sound
Install Scrcpy:
sudo apt install Scrcpy Sndcpy: download the latest release and extract the files
Mirror Screen with Scrcpy First, go to your device settings and enable developer mode then, connect your Android device to your computer with your charger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH into Termux</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/termux-ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/termux-ssh/</guid>
      <description>Just do the following steps:
Install OpenSSH on Termux: pkg upgrade &amp;amp;&amp;amp; pkg install openssh Setup a password for Termux: passwd Get your username: whoami Start SSH server sshd Connect! From your computer ssh like usual; the default port Termux uses for SSH is 8022.
example:
my IP is 192.168.0.10
my username: u0_a231
so my command would be:
ssh u0_a231@192.168.0.10 -p 8022 Video your browser doesn&#39;t support video tag.  Right click and check &amp;ldquo;Show all controls&amp;rdquo; to see video controls*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Scambaiting</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/advanced-scambaiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/advanced-scambaiting/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer DO THESE THINGS AT YOUR OWN RISK
IT IS NOT RECOMMENDED TO DO THESE THINGS AS SCAMBAITING
Reverse Anydesk connection First you have to let them connect to your PC, make sure you see their anydesk ID before accepting their connection request.
then send them anydesk request from another PC or the host PC (if you are using VM) at the same time, when accepting their anydesk connection request. If you time it perfecting and you have an inexperienced scammer, you should be connected to the scammer&amp;rsquo;s PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started - PhoneInFoga</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/phoneinfoga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/phoneinfoga/</guid>
      <description>Brief PhoneInFoga - Information gathering &amp;amp; OSINT framework for phone numbers.
This install guide is specific to Debian/Ubuntu machines, for other installation options, visit PhoneInfoga&amp;rsquo;s install page.
Install Installation documentation
run these command:
Install the latest version
curl -sSL https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sundowndev/phoneinfoga/master/support/scripts/install | bash Confirm/Check install
./phoneinfoga version Copy it to path for global install
sudo mv ./phoneinfoga /usr/bin/phoneinfoga Usage Scan with &amp;ldquo;phoneinfoga -n [NUMBER WITH COUNTRY CODE]&amp;rdquo;
Example:
phoneinfoga serve -n +1234567891 The output is kinda weird and messy so using the web GUI is a better way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Server on LAN</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/hugo-lan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/hugo-lan/</guid>
      <description>Brief [IP-ADD] is your local IP address.
Command use this command instead of &amp;ldquo;hugo server&amp;rdquo;
hugo server --bind [IP-ADD] --baseURL http://[IP-ADD] Conclusion visit http://[IP-ADD] from any device on your LAN to view the temporary hugo site.
that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixed - Termux Repository Under Maintenance Issue</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/termux-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/termux-repo/</guid>
      <description>Error error looks something like this:
This error usually occurs on older version of termux specially when you install termux from Play Store. It is recommended to install it from F-Droid since it has the latest &amp;amp; greatest version.
Fix visit []Termux on F-Droid](https://f-droid.org/en/packages/com.termux/) and install the APK normally.
NOTE: INSTALL THE F-DROID APPLICATION IS NOT IMPORTANT
that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Scambaiting</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/scambaiting101/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/scambaiting101/</guid>
      <description>Getting started Keep in mind that you are dealing with people who are criminals, giving your personal information is stupid to say the least. Making a fake persona here is helpful and what most people do.
A VPN isn&amp;rsquo;t important since there is just enough they can do by finding your IP. A free vpn I suggest is cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s WARP furthermore, there are many cheap VPNs which work great: Private Internet Access &amp;amp; OpenVPN are two of many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Threat Intelligence Tools</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/threatinteltools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/threatinteltools/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/threatinteltools
Task 1-2 no answer needed
Task 3 - UrlScan.io answers are from the image right above*
Question 1: What is TryHackMe&amp;rsquo;s Cisco Umbrella Rank? ~ 345612
Question 2: How many domains did UrlScan.io identify? ~ 13
Question 3: What is the main domain registrar listed? ~ NAMECHEAP INC
Question 4: What is the main IP address identified? ~ 2606:4700:10::ac43:1b0a
Task 4 - Abuse.ch Question 1: The IOC 212.192.246.30:5555 is linked to which malware on ThreatFox?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Introduction to Antivirus</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/introtoav/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/introtoav/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/introtoav
Task 1 - Introduction no answer needed
Task 2 - Antivirus Software answers are from the text*
Question 1: What was the virus name that infected John McAfee&amp;rsquo;s PC? ~ brain
Question 2: Which PC Antivirus vendor implemented the first AV software on the market? ~ McAfee
Question 3: Antivirus software is a _____-based security solution. ~ host
Task 3 - Antivirus Features answers are from the text*</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UFW | Firewall on Linux Systems</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/linux-firewall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/linux-firewall/</guid>
      <description>Uncomplicated Firewall (UFW) is an easy and beginner friendly firewall for linux systems.
Install sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install ufw Verify Install sudo ufw status Basic Blocks sudo ufw default deny incoming sudo ufw default allow outgoing Enable Firewall sudo ufw enable Blocking Ports you can block any port by &amp;ldquo;sudo ufw deny PORT&amp;rdquo; for example, to block port 76 type:
sudo ufw deny 76 Allow Ports you can allow any port by &amp;ldquo;sudo ufw allow PORT&amp;rdquo; for example, to allow port 22 (default SSH port) type:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Viruses From Windows</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/remove-viruses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/remove-viruses/</guid>
      <description>Tron is a all in one program to remove any viruses from windows and get windows &amp;ldquo;back on it&amp;rsquo;s feet&amp;rdquo;
Install https://www.reddit.com/r/TronScript/
Reference Chris Titus has a great video on this explaining everything so I will just link it.
  that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better APT</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/better-apt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/better-apt/</guid>
      <description>why not APT? APT has slow mirrors, APT isn&amp;rsquo;t optimised for performance right out of the box, rolling back updates or installs is pain because there is no concept of history and last but not the least, the look of APT is just mehhh.
Nala is just better. Nala fixes all these problems right from the start while having APT is the backend.
Install add repository
echo &amp;#34;deb http://deb.volian.org/volian/ scar main&amp;#34; | sudo tee /etc/apt/sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark mode for Instagram Web</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/dark-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/dark-instagram/</guid>
      <description>just add &amp;ldquo;?theme=dark&amp;rdquo; add the end of instagram url
for example, www.instagram.com?theme=dark
that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Linux Modules</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/linuxmodules/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/linuxmodules/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/linuxmodules
Task 1: Let&amp;rsquo;s Introduce No answer needed
Task 2: du No answer needed
Task 3: Grep, Egrep, Fgrep Read the above No answer needed
Question 1: Is there a difference between egrep and fgrep? (Yea/Nay) ~ Yea
Question 2: Which flag do you use to list out all the lines NOT containing the &amp;lsquo;PATTERN&amp;rsquo;? ~ -v
Download the above given file and answer the following questions. ~ No answer needed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Burp Suite: Repeater</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/burpsuiterepeater/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/burpsuiterepeater/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/burpsuiterepeater
Task 1: Introduction Outline No answer needed
Task 2: Repeater What is Repeater? No answer needed
Task 3: Repeater Basic Usage? No answer needed
Task 4: Repeater Views Question 1: No answer needed
Question 2: Which view option displays the response in the same format as your browser would? ~ Render
Task 5: Repeater Inspector No answer needed
Task 6: Practical Example No answer needed
Question 3: Send the request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Burp Suite: The Basics</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/burpsuitebasics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/burpsuitebasics/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/burpsuitebasics
Task 1: Introduction Outline No answer needed
Task 2: Getting Started What is Burp Suite? Question 1: Which edition of Burp Suite will we be using in this module? ~ Burp Suite Community
Question 2: Which edition of Burp Suite runs on a server and provides constant scanning for target web apps? ~ burp suite enterprise
Question 3: Burp Suite is frequently used when attacking web applications and ______ applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | DNS Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/dnsmanipulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/dnsmanipulation/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/dnsmanipulation
Task 1: Introduction No answer needed
Task 2: Installation No answer needed
Task 3: [Setup] Custom Public DNS Server No answer needed
Task 4: What is DNS? Question 1: If you were on Windows, what command could you use to query a txt record for &amp;ldquo;youtube.com&amp;rdquo;? ~ nslookup -type=txt youtube.com
Question 2: If you were on Linux, what command could you use to query a txt record for &amp;lsquo;facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Red Team Engagements</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/redteamengagements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/redteamengagements/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/redteamengagements
Task 1: Introduction No answer needed
Task 2: Defining Scope and Objectives Question 1-2: No answer needd
Question 3: What CIDR range is permitted to be attacked? ~ 10.0.4.0/22
Question 4: Is the use of white cards permitted? (Y/N) ~ Y
Question 5: Are you permitted to access &amp;ldquo;*.bethechange.xyz?&amp;rdquo; (Y/N) ~ N
Task 3: Rules of Engagement Question 1: Once downloaded, read the sample document and answer the questions below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Red Team Recon</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/redteamrecon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/redteamrecon/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/redteamrecon
Task 1: Introduction No answer needed
Task 2: Taxonomy of Reconnaissance No answer needed
Task 3: Built-in Tools Question 1: When was thmredteam.com created (registered)? (YYYY-MM-DD) ~ 2021-09-24
whois thmredteam.com Question 2: To how many IPv4 addresses does clinic.thmredteam.com resolve? ~ 2
host clinic.thmredteam.com Question 3: To how many IPv6 addresses does clinic.thmredteam.com resolve? ~ 2
host clinic.thmredteam.com Task 4: Advanced Searching Question 1: How would you search using Google for xls indexed for http://clinic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Cryptography for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/cryptographyfordummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/cryptographyfordummies/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/cryptographyfordummies
Task 1: Intro No answer needed
Task 2: Types of cryptography Question 1: What type of cryptography is more secure? ~ asymmetric
Question 2: What type of cryptography is faster? ~ symmetric
Question 3: What type of cryptography will a Bank site use? ~ symmetric
Question 4: What will you use to encrypt your messages in asymmetric cryptography? ~ public key
Question 5: What will you use to decrypt messages in asymmetric cryptography?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Common Attacks</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/commonattacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/commonattacks/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/commonattacks
Task 1: Information Introduction Question 1: Let&amp;rsquo;s get started! No answer needed
Task 2: Common Attacks Social Engineering Question 1: Read the task information and watch the attached videos No answer needed
Question 2: What was the original target of Stuxnet? ~ iran nuclear programme
Task 3: Common Attacks Social Engineering Phishing Question 1: Click the green &amp;ldquo;View Site&amp;rdquo; button at the top of this task if you haven&amp;rsquo;t already done so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Website Hosting</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/hosting/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer There are many ways to host static website for free. In this guide we will use github as a hosting platform. Github can only host static websites*
Prerequisites  Github account Code for your website  Main Step 1: Click the &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; icon and click &amp;ldquo;New repository&amp;rdquo; Step 2: Set basic info Keep a name for your repository. Adding &amp;lsquo;.github.io&amp;quot; at the end of your repo name is important</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | tmux</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/rptmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/rptmux/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/rptmux
Task 1: Screens wishes it was this cool Question 1: First things first, let&amp;rsquo;s go ahead and install tmux. This can be done on Ubuntu/Kali with the command: apt-get install tmux No answer needed
Question 2: Once tmux is installed, let&amp;rsquo;s launch a new session. What command do we use to launch a new session without a custom name? ~ tmux
Question 3: All tmux commands start with a keyboard button combination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Bypassing UAC</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/bypassinguac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/bypassinguac/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/bypassinguac
steps won&amp;rsquo;t be explained since the room has walkthrough*
Task 1: Introduction Question 1: Click and continue learning! No answer needed
Task 2: User Account Control (UAC) Question 1: What is the highest integrity level (IL) available on Windows? ~ system
Question 2: What is the IL associated with an administrator&amp;rsquo;s elevated token? ~ high
Question 3: What is the full name of the service in charge of dealing with UAC elevation requests?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Intro to Digital Forensics</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/introdigitalforensics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/introdigitalforensics/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/introdigitalforensics
Task 1: Introduction to Digital Forensics Question 1: Consider the desk in the photo above. In addition to the smartphone, camera, and SD cards, what would be interesting for digital forensics? ~ laptop
Task 2: Digital Forensics Process Question 1: It is essential to keep track of who is handling it at any point in time to ensure that evidence is admissible in the court of law. What is the name of the documentation that would help establish that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSL Certificate with Certbot</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/ssl-apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/ssl-apache/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Debian, Apache2, Snapd, Certbot
Install sudo apt update sudo apt install snapd -y install certbot
sudo snap install certbot --classic Create symbolic link so you can run certbot command from the terminal
sudo ln -s /snap/bin/certbot /usr/bin/certbot Run certbot command
sudo certbot --apache you can change &amp;ldquo;&amp;ndash;apache&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;&amp;ndash;nginx&amp;rdquo; if you are using nginx instead of apache
Getting the Cert Enter your valid email address so certbot can contact you for renewal and security notices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Debian comepletely from DualBoot</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/remove-dualboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/remove-dualboot/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Windows 10 PC
I - Delete partition Right click on the start button (bottom left corner) and click on &amp;ldquo;Disk Management&amp;rdquo;
ideally there should be 2 linux partition, one swap area and other is main disk partition. These are the two partitions I have
right click on one of them and click on &amp;ldquo;Delete Volume&amp;rdquo;
click yes on the pop up
repeat the last two steps for the second partition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disable Updates</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/disable-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/disable-updates/</guid>
      <description>Brief Windows Update BLocker(Wub) - A minimal tool to block windows updates.
Download You can download the latest version from the official website
Extract the zip file and open the Wub_x64.exe file as adminstator
Here click the second option (Disable updates)
Once you have disabled the updates the app will look like this
You can close the app now.
If you check for updates now in windows settings you will see this error</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Updates on Linux</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/auto-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/auto-updates/</guid>
      <description>Brief Unattendeed Upgrades - Automatic installation of security upgrades on apt based systems.
install sudo apt update sudo apt install unattended-upgrades -y Enable Automatic Updates enable automatic updates by:
sudo dpkg-reconfigure -plow unattended-upgrades  &amp;ldquo;-plow&amp;rdquo; is to set prorioty as low for unattended upgrades.  select &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo; from these options:
Other config/sources For more about configuration, go through this blog by Hayden James.
that’s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Bot in Python (without API)</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/twitter-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/twitter-bot/</guid>
      <description>Brief I wanted to make a python script which would share my latest blog on Twitter &amp;amp; Linkedin, So I made one.
We will use firefox as the browser thus, we would need geckodriver. The tutorial assumes you already have it.
Code Breakdown Modules from selenium import webdriver from selenium.webdriver.firefox.options import Options import warnings import time   We are gonna use Selenium for webscrapping
  options so we can open browser in headless mode</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nmap quick start</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/nmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/nmap/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER THIS TOOL SHOULD ONLY BE USED FOR EDUCATIONAL OR ETHICAL HACKING PURPOSE. MISUSE OF THIS TOOL WILL LEAD TO PROSECUTION.
Brief Nmap - the network mapper.
install Debian sudo apt install nmap Snap sudo snap install nmap Basic Arguments 1. pingging whole network -sP nmap -sP &amp;lt;ip/24&amp;gt; For example:
nmap -sP 172.67.208.3/24 2. Simple TCP scan A TCP is what makes the internet. TCP aka Transmission Control Protocol is a standard that defines how to establish and maintain a network conversation via thethree way handshake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email forwarding with cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/email-forwarding-cloudflare/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/email-forwarding-cloudflare/</guid>
      <description>BRIEF You can forward email with pretty much any domain provider but in this case I am using Cloudflare.
By the end of this article, you will be able to send and receive email from a custom email address that uses your domain name.
You will need to enable 2 Step verification on your google account for this to work.
Step 1: Setup Cloudflaee The first step is to setup cloudflare so it can route email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Red Team Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/redteamfundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/redteamfundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/redteamfundamentals
Task 1: Introduction Question 1: Click to continue to the next task No Answer Needed
Task 2: Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Tests Limitations Question 1: Would vulnerability assessments prepare us to detect a real attacker on our networks? (Yay/Nay) ~ Nay
Question 2: During a penetration test, are you concerned about being detected by the client? (Yay/Nay) ~ Nay
Question 3: Highly organised groups of skilled attackers are nowadays referred to as … ~ advanced persistent theats</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install BeEF on Debian</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/beef-debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/beef-debian/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER THIS TOOL SHOULD ONLY BE USED FOR EDUCATIONAL OR ETHICAL HACKING PURPOSE. MISUSE OF THIS TOOL WILL LEAD TO PROSECUTION.
BRIEF BeEF is short for The Browser Exploitation Framework. It is a penetration testing tool that focuses on the web browser.
Step 1: installing dependencies Before installing anything update your repositories.
sudo apt update -y Ruby, Ruby-dev and Git is required for BeEF. Install them using:
sudo apt install ruby ruby-dev git -y Step 2: Installation Clone BeEF repo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Wreath</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/wreath/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/wreath
Task 1-4: Intro No Answer Needed
Task 5: Webserver Enumeration Question 1: How many of the first 15000 ports are open on the target? ~ 4
Question 2: What OS does nmap think is running? ~ CentOS
Question 3: Open the IP in your browser — what site does the sever try to redirect you to? ~ https://thomaswreath.thm
Question 4: What is Thomas’ mobile phone number? ~ +447821548812</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>View Saved WiFi Passwords</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/saved-wifi-pwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 23:39:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/saved-wifi-pwd/</guid>
      <description>Brief A way to see WiFi password for linux.
Command cd /etc/NetworkManager/system-connections/ &amp;amp;&amp;amp; sudo cat [ssid] or use this script
that’s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Networking</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/bpnetworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/bpnetworking/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/bpnetworking
Task 1: Kinda like a street address, just cooler. Question 1: How many categories of IPV4 addresses are there? ~ 5
Question 2: Which type is for research *Looking for a letter rather than a number here? ~ E
Question 3: How many private address ranges are there? ~ 3
Question 4: Which private range is typically used by businesses? ~ A
Question 5: There are two commn default private ranges for home routers, what is the first one?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | VIM</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/toolboxvim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/toolboxvim/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/toolboxvim
Task 1: Task 1 Question 1: Install VIM No Answer Needed
Question 2: Launch VIM No Answer Needed
Task 2: Task 2 Question 1: How do wew enter &amp;ldquo;INSERT&amp;rdquo; mode? ~ i
Question 2: How do we start entering text into our new Vim document? ~ typing
Question 3: How do we return t command mode? ~ esc
Question 4: How do we move the cursor left? ~ h</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | Basic Pentesting</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/basicpentestingjt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/basicpentestingjt/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/basicpentestingjt
Task 1: Web App Testing and Privilege Esclation Question 1: Question 1: Deploy he machine and connect to our network No Answer Needed
Question 2: Find the services exposed by the machine No Answer Needed
nmap -Pn -sC -sV -oN nmap &amp;lt;machine-ip&amp;gt; Question 3: What is the name of the hidden directory on the web server(enter name without /)? ~ development
gobuster dir -u &amp;lt;machine-ip&amp;gt; -w &amp;lt;[dir-to-directory-list-2.3-medium.txt](https://gitlab.com/kalilinux/packages/dirbuster/-/raw/kali/master/directory-list-2.3-medium.txt)&amp;gt; wordlist used^</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows on Linux</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/windows-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/windows-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Brief Some things just are better on windows than linux thus having a windows virtual machine(VM) is a great idea specially when daily driving linux.
We will be using Vert Manager to use windows 7 on vanilla Debian linux however, this will work on any Debian based system i.e Ubuntu.
Machine I am using: Step 1: Confirm virtualization Open terminal and type
grep -o &amp;quot;vm\|sum&amp;quot; /proc/cpuinfo here the command outputs ‘vmx’ but if u are not using intel processor it will show ‘SVM’ instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THM | nmap</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/furthernmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/write-ups/furthernmap/</guid>
      <description>Room https://tryhackme.com/room/furthernmap
Task 1: Deploy Question 1: Deploy the attached VM No Answer Needed
Task 2: Introduction Question 1: What networking constructs are used to direct traffic to the right application on a server? ~ Ports
Question 2: How many of these are available on any network-enabled computer? ~ 65535
Question 3: [Research] How many of these are considered &amp;ldquo;well-known&amp;rdquo;? (These are the &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; numbers mentioned in the task) ~ 1024</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>   Contact Us  
strong { font-size: 40px; }  You can email us on info@mansoorbarri.com  or Fill in the form below to send us any queries 
    Send a message    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/twitter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/linkedin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/tryhackme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/tryhackme/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/twitter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/.htaccess</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/.htaccess</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/_redirects</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/_redirects</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> </title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/contact-filled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/contact-filled/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for contacting mansoorbarri.com! One of us will with you shortly. Return to main page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About mansoorbarri.com</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Mission &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not just about the technology for us. It&amp;rsquo;s about making the effort to assist. As a result, everything we do is geared toward making your business and IT systems more cost effective. So, as soon as you engage us, we engage our brains.&amp;rdquo;
Unlike the market, where customer service means long lines, inadequate and overworked employees, we strive to provide exemplary service tailored to your needs.
Why Choose Us?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Mansoor Barri owns and operates the website mansoorbarri.com, which provides this service.
At mansoorbarri.com, accessible from mansoorbarri.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by mansoorbarri.com and how we use it.
Log Files mansoorbarri.com follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services&#39; analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
