<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AdventOfCyber4 on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/adventofcyber4/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AdventOfCyber4 on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/adventofcyber4/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>THM | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/</guid>
      <description>Room Advent Of Cyber 4
Chapters Day 1 Someone&amp;rsquo;s coming to town!
Day 2 Santa&amp;rsquo;s Naughty &amp;amp; Nice Log
Day 3 Nothing escapes detective McRed
Day 4 Scanning through the snow
Day 5 He knows when you&amp;rsquo;re awake
Day 6 It&amp;rsquo;s beginning to look a lot like phishing
Day 7 Maldocs roasting on an open fire
Day 8 Last Christmas I gave you my ETH
Day 9 Dock the halls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 13 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday13/</guid>
      <description>What is the &amp;ldquo;Percent Packets&amp;rdquo; value of the &amp;ldquo;Hypertext Transfer Protocol&amp;rdquo;? 0.3 Which port number has received more than 1000 packets? 3389 What is the service name of the used protocol that received more than 1000 packets? rdp What are the domain names? bestfestivalcompany[.]thm,cdn[.]bandityeti[.]thm What are the names of the requested files? favicon[.]ico,mysterygift[.]exe Which IP address downloaded the executable file? 10[.]10[.]29[.]186 Which domain address hosts the malicious file? cdn[.]bandityeti[.]thm What is the &amp;ldquo;user-agent&amp;rdquo; value used to download the non-executable file?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 12 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday12/</guid>
      <description>What is the architecture of the malware sample? (32-bit/64-bit) 64-bit What is the packer used in the malware sample? (format: lowercase) upx What is the compiler used to build the malware sample? (format: lowercase) nim How many MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK techniques have been discovered attributed to the DISCOVERY tactic? 2 What is the registry key abused by the malware? HKCU\Software\Microsoft\Windows\CurrentVersion\Run What is the value written on the registry key based on the previous question?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday11/</guid>
      <description>What is the Windows version number that the memory image captured? 10 What is the name of the binary/gift that secret Santa left? mysterygift.ex What is the Process ID (PID) of this binary? 2040 Dump the contents of this binary. How many files are dumped? 16 that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday10/</guid>
      <description>What is the Guard&amp;rsquo;s flag? THM{5_star_Fl4gzzz} What is the Yeti&amp;rsquo;s flag? THM{yetiyetiyetiflagflagflag} that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 9 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday9/</guid>
      <description>Deploy the attached VM, and wait a few minutes. What ports are open? 80 What framework is the web application developed with? laravel What CVE is the application vulnerable to? CVE-2021-3129 What command can be used to upgrade the last opened session to a Meterpreter session? sessions -u -1 What file indicates a session has been opened within a Docker container? /.dockerenv What file often contains useful credentials for web applications?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 8 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday8/</guid>
      <description>What flag is found after attacking the provided EtherStore Contract? flag{411_ur_37h_15_m1n3} that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 7 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday7/</guid>
      <description>What is the version of CyberChef found in the attached VM? 9.49.0 How many recipes were used to extract URLs from the malicious doc? 10 We found a URL that was downloading a suspicious file; what is the name of that malware? mysterygift.exe What is the last defanged URL of the bandityeti domain found in the last step? hxxps[://]cdn[.]bandityeti[.]THM/files/index/ What is the ticket found in one of the domains? (Format: Domain/&amp;lt;GOLDEN_FLAG&amp;gt;) THM_MYSTERY_FLAG that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 6 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday6/</guid>
      <description>What is the email address of the sender? chief.elf@santaclaus.thm What is the return address? murphy.evident@bandityeti.thm On whose behalf was the email sent? Chief Elf What is the X-spam score? 3 What is hidden in the value of the Message-ID field? AoC2022_Email_Analysis What is the reputation result of the sender&amp;rsquo;s email address? RISKY What is the filename of the attachment? Division_of_labour-Load_share_plan.doc What is the hash value of the attachment? 0827bb9a2e7c0628b82256759f0f888ca1abd6a2d903acdb8e44aca6a1a03467 What is the second tactic marked in the Mitre ATT&amp;amp;CK section?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 5 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday5/</guid>
      <description>Use Hydra to find the VNC password of the target with IP address MACHINE_IP. What is the password? 1q2w3e4r Using a VNC client on the AttackBox, connect to the target of IP address MACHINE_IP. What is the flag written on the target’s screen? THM{I_SEE_YOUR_SCREEN} If you liked the topics presented in this task, check out these rooms next: Protocols and Servers 2, Hydra, Password Attacks, John the Ripper. No answer needed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 4 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday4/</guid>
      <description>What is the name of the HTTP server running on the remote host? Apache What is the name of the service running on port 22 on the QA server? ssh What flag can you find after successfully accessing the Samba service? {THM_SANTA_SMB_SERVER} What is the password for the username santahr? santa25 If you want to learn more scanning techniques, we have a module dedicated to Nmap! No answer needed
that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday3/</guid>
      <description>What is the name of the Registrar for the domain santagift.shop? NAMECHEAP INC Find the website&amp;rsquo;s source code (repository) on github.com and open the file containing sensitive credentials. Can you find the flag? {THM_OSINT_WORKS} What is the name of the file containing passwords? config.php What is the name of the QA server associated with the website? qa.santagift.shop What is the DB_PASSWORD that is being reused between the QA and PROD environments?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday2/</guid>
      <description>Ensure you are connected to the deployable machine in this task. No answer needed
Use the ls command to list the files present in the current directory. How many log files are present? 2 Elf McSkidy managed to capture the logs generated by the web server. What is the name of this log file? webserver.log Begin investigating the log file from question #3 to answer the following questions. No answer needed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day 1 | Advent Of Cyber 4</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/writeups/adventofcyber4/aocday1/</guid>
      <description>Who is the adversary that attacked Santa&amp;rsquo;s network this year? The Bandit Yeti What&amp;rsquo;s the flag that they left behind? THM{IT&#39;S A Y3T1 CHR1$TMA$} Looking to learn more? Check out the rooms on Unified Kill Chain, Cyber Kill Chain, MITRE, or the whole Cyber Defence Frameworks module! No answer needed
that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
