<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tips on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tips on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Use One Mouse-Keyboard On Two Systems</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/one-keyboard-mouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/how-to/one-keyboard-mouse/</guid>
      <description>Brief Barrier is an open-source software application that allows many computers to share a mouse and keyboard. I&amp;rsquo;m controlling a Windows machine with a Debian-based machine.
Installing Barrier Barrier must be installed on both the Windows and Debian-based machines before it can be used. The most recent version of Barrier can be downloaded from the official website here.
Installing Barrier on Windows To install Barrier on Windows, follow these steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Practicies To Keep Yourself Safe Online</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/best-practicies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/articles/best-practicies/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few simple IT tasks that people should think about doing to protect and secure their devices and personal information:
  Updating software and security patches: It is critical to update your operating system and other software on a regular basis to ensure that you have the most recent security patches and features.
  Backing up data: Backing up important files and data on a regular basis can protect against loss or damage in the event of a hardware failure or a cyber attack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
