<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Edit HTML Files With Python</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/py-html-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/py-html-editor/</guid>
      <description>Context I have a email template which is made using &amp;lt;table&amp;gt; tags in HTML and its a sad job to edit and add messages to send on email. I wanted to change it to a template which does not use &amp;lt;table&amp;gt; however doing so made it really non responsive which is not ideally as emails are viewed on various devices.
Solution I thought of making a python script which adds your message at a specific place on the HTML fiile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting PNG to WebP Images in Python: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/pngtowebp-explain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/pngtowebp-explain/</guid>
      <description>This article explains the code for a PNG to WebP converter in Python. The code utilizes the Python Imaging Library (PIL) to open and manipulate images, and the os and sys modules to work with files and directories.
Code Explanation The code starts with an ASCII art of the text &amp;ldquo;code by Mansoor Barri&amp;rdquo; printed to the console using the print() function.
Next, the required modules are imported:
from PIL import Image import os import sys The Image module is imported from PIL, which provides functions for opening, manipulating, and saving images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convert Python files to Windows executable files</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/py-to-exe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/py-to-exe/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites You should have all the modules installed before compiling You should have all the requirements for the python file before compiling it Install Nuitka on Windows Go to Go to nuitka.net/download/windows which will download a .msi file
Run the file and click on &amp;ldquo;More info&amp;rdquo;
Click on &amp;ldquo;Run anyway&amp;rdquo;
Click on &amp;ldquo;Install for all users&amp;rdquo; then click &amp;ldquo;Next&amp;rdquo;
Specify the python 3.9 compiler, its easier to use the Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Bot in Python (without API)</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/twitter-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/twitter-bot/</guid>
      <description>Brief I wanted to make a python script which would share my latest blog on Twitter &amp;amp; Linkedin, So I made one.
We will use firefox as the browser thus, we would need geckodriver. The tutorial assumes you already have it.
Code Breakdown Modules from selenium import webdriver from selenium.webdriver.firefox.options import Options import warnings import time We are gonna use Selenium for webscrapping
options so we can open browser in headless mode</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
