<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Website on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Website on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Adsense</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/guides/google-adsense/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/guides/google-adsense/</guid>
      <description>Context Google adsense can be a great way to maintain a website as the earning aren&amp;rsquo;t not much to sustain a household but can be enough to sustain a website and everything related to maintain a website (hosting, CMS etc)
Google Adsense Google adsense can be a great way to start your journey however Google is quite picky with what is suitable for their adsense platform.
I was rejected several times over a year with little to no information about what is wrong with my site; I was accepted finally after using multiple tools and tips from previous website owners like TonyTeachesTech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahrefs: The SEO Speacialist</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/guides/ahrefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/guides/ahrefs/</guid>
      <description>Context I have been using Ahrefs for almost a year now which lead to my site (mansoorbarri.com) being the top 3 for the keyword &amp;ldquo;Mansoor Barri&amp;rdquo; on Google &amp;amp; DuckDuckGo.
Ahrefs Setup Sign Up Go to https://Ahrefs.com/signup/ Follow the signup instructions If plan is asked, select the free plan Connecting Your Site Verification methods could include adding a meta tag to your website&amp;rsquo;s HTML, uploading a verification file to your server, or modifying your DNS records.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
