<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newsletter on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newsletter on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cyber War</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/cyber-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/cyber-war/</guid>
      <description>baingen,
It&amp;rsquo;s been a good week for the website; there was a post every other day with guides as well as newsletters so it was a slay. College has been pretty boring too since I already know most of the stuff so I don&amp;rsquo;t even know what to do in lectures. tbh i&amp;rsquo;m just waiting for the programming/coding topic to start.
⚠ War we all know what has been happening past week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come Back</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/come-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/come-back/</guid>
      <description>Halo again,
Its been more than a week since I posted so the website is quite dry, I have some ideas for this week so this might just be a come back from being dry-asf.
🎮 | Game Development I wanted to try game development since I had this idea and wanted to try it before I regret and its no longer relevent. I won&amp;rsquo;t really say the idea of the game for obvious reasons however it was a multiplayer game which required me to develop an API i think which was just a big turn off to be honest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Block</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/creative-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/creative-block/</guid>
      <description>Been a while, I didn&amp;rsquo;t send anything to you or on the website because I fr don&amp;rsquo;t know what to post. At a point, I did have some ideas but my laziness did not write them down and of course I forgot. I am working on a couple of things which might be informative so there will be posts however the streak is broken now which is sad and I don&amp;rsquo;t plan to make it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assign-mint</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/assign-mint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/assign-mint/</guid>
      <description>Ho Ho Ho,
I started this instead of blog since I wanted to have something a bit more personal and not just something which is there on the internet for literally everyone. This is &amp;ldquo;public&amp;rdquo; but its like this close community.
College Since my sister did her uni before me, she found assignments pretty hard especially with similarity and just stuff which is supposed to be similar like stats, titles, questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academia</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/academia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/academia/</guid>
      <description>Update Since the last blog, adsense is still pending however I have planned a guide about adsense and what I used till now to get at least nearer to being accepted by Google. Will be live when I get accepted officially since I might use something new in the meanwhile.
GCSE Got the expected grades however they increased the grade boundaries to pre-covid level even though this batch was in COVID in year 9 but slay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamline</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/streamline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/streamline/</guid>
      <description>Context Decided to post blogs weekly probably which would be a bit informal and just about how things are going and my plans with mansoorbarri.com as the normal &amp;ldquo;blogging&amp;rdquo; wouldn&amp;rsquo;t fit in articles, guides or write-ups.
Mentioning the categories reminds me of how there are just two categories now Guides &amp;amp; Blogs making it easier for the end-user to just navigate through stuff. Since the change, I will be posting write-ups on Medium and the normal articles will be on the company website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of 2020</title>
      <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2020/</guid>
      <description>Goals for 2022 Posting how-to guides on mansoor.cf everyday Learning and growing in CyberSecurity making mansoorbarri.com a IT company Getting a job It started off really well at the beginning of this year, but as I got busier, it became a weekly thing, then monthly, and finally a seasonal thing where I would post 5 guides every 2-3 months. However, in the last quarter, I really expanded this into a polished product, which I did not expect at all.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
