<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Newsletters on Mansoor Barri</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Newsletters on Mansoor Barri</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Mansoor Barri</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>My Vim Journey</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/vim-journey/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/vim-journey/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Been a while, but I wanted to take a break from everything once again because I was cooking a idea. More on this later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;vim&#34;&gt;Vim&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started Vim motions at the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/vim/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;start of this year&lt;/a&gt; because I wanted to optimise my work even more; before it was by increasing my typing speed to 110 but now its vim. Long story short, I saw Primagen be a god at typing &amp;amp; got motivated to really drill down on vim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as of now, I am pretty confident with doing basic typing and editing  and its getting better with the help of vimtutor- which I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about which is crazy to me now that I think about it. Its basically a gamified version of learning vim and its kinda fun except you have to do it pretty regularly for it to actually stick to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;wait, did vim actually help?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mansoorbarri.com/img/newsletter/2024/vim-journey/coding-stats.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;screenshot of Wakatime&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;thats my usage as of now and its pretty good. I feel much more productive and it feels like I can do a lot so I don&amp;rsquo;t know to be honest. Time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-project&#34;&gt;New project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I heard &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://christitus.com&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Chris Titus&lt;/a&gt; say that he would wanna work on a Linux version of his tool, winutil. and I had the same idea a while ago (&lt;em&gt;probably last year&lt;/em&gt;) and I tried making it but it didn&amp;rsquo;t go well since I tried to make GUI first &amp;amp; that too with python.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time I am making terminal version first and then later on do the GUI as well as support other distros like arch &amp;amp; fedora. As of today, it has some tweaks and apps to install, check it out and do let me know if you like it or have any feedback: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/mansoorbarri/lintil&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://github.com/mansoorbarri/lintil&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;journal&#34;&gt;Journal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanna start journalling but I have said that various times and have tried it too but stop doing it after the third time so I don&amp;rsquo;t think there is a point of doing it again. But, I don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;its kind of confusing because I don&amp;rsquo;t want to make it all fancy or do it religiously or have an app for it. Basically, I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what I want except that, I want to be able to journal directly from my brain. I think i need help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it for now to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Productive = Accustomed</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/productive-=-accustomed/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/productive-=-accustomed/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi long time no see,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was just watching YouTube like usual and saw &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aWGviOMQqSw&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;em&gt;this video&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and thought to myself if productivity apps depend on how accustomed you are with the app. This would be that there is no &amp;ldquo;productivity app&amp;rdquo; :0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here me out, I have experienced this too. You wake up and think about all the things you can do today and you even start doing some and get through half of the list but then realise that you haven&amp;rsquo;t ticked off the stuff from your fancy to-do list app so now you open the app and tick off everything you have done just to realise that you have done everything which was not important and/or had a deadline in the distant future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://prod-files-secure.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c955c27b-72fa-4c77-8acb-d92a8ca39896/f9afd8c7-302f-4280-8002-e4d2c3c6b419/Untitled.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Untitled&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crazy. absolutely disgusting. You can have look around YouTube and find this pattern as well:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@aliabdaal&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Ali Abdaal&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; swears by notion because it helps him be productive - in reality, its just that he has been using it since his &lt;em&gt;doctor days&lt;/em&gt; and now he has a dozen of notion pages with all his stuff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@mkbhd&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;MKBHD&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; can not live without a to-do list and uses ticktick for the longest time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@casey&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Casey Neistat&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; does not use any of the apps and just does things off of his head.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@vanneistat&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Van Neistart&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; loves to use sticky notes for everything: labelling, to-do, tasks, calenders, everything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope I don&amp;rsquo;t feel weird thinking this but seriously, if thats the case then there is no PRODUCTIVITY APP. And no, I am not saying that these apps are bad, in fact, this newsletter was just a idea in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/momentum/laookkfknpbbblfpciffpaejjkokdgca&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Momentum&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; then brought into &lt;em&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://notion.so&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Notion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for the &amp;ldquo;writing process&amp;rdquo; and then sent to &lt;em&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://convertkit.com/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;ConvertKit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; followed by &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://mansoorbarri.com&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;my website&lt;/a&gt;. So I am guilty of the productivity bs as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be honest, the &amp;ldquo;productivity&amp;rdquo; tag just gets thrown around a lot as a way to class something which is even slightly office related. For example, Notion - a all in one app where you can do pretty much everything but thats what M365 says too so you are better-off calling it the ultimate productivity app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;in conclusion, just use whatever suits you best and what makes you actually do stuff. Either it be having everything in Notion and living day to day like a robot or just do things off your head while you are creating a movie every single day for 800 days. Both gets things done and everyone will still call you &lt;em&gt;productive.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Firstlance</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/firstlance/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/firstlance/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I have been busy with things other than website and the newsletter. I got a gig on Fiverr after trying for it for months, but to be honest, its the first time I actually did things right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some things that helped:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;motivation&#34;&gt;Motivation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its important to have things that actually do motivate you. I didn&amp;rsquo;t really think about Fiverr or any other freelancing platform until I saw this tweet by &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://twitter.com/yb_fedev/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Julia&lt;/a&gt; which just happened randomly but it just sparked motivation. Quite random but works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tweet:
&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;5 tips that helped me to get my first client on Upwork👇🏼&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Julia👩‍💻 (@yb_fedev) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/yb_fedev/status/1752610754702843977?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;January 31, 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;niche&#34;&gt;Niche&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have probably heard it many times &amp;amp;&amp;amp; I found it quite cliche that you have to chOoSe a NiChE but it does more than we think. I was trying for web develoment, cyber or just IT managing gigs however this time around, I created a gig about converting web designs to a Hugo site which is quite a specific use case. Few weeks later, I got my first order.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the gig: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.fiverr.com/barri_/convert-your-website-to-a-hugo-website&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.fiverr.com/barri_/convert-your-website-to-a-hugo-website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;sweetspot&#34;&gt;Sweetspot&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pricing matters a lot especially on Fiverr. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to lowball or highball but find a sweetspot which is not soo much for a first timer but also not soo cheap that it feels unconvincing. Over time you will probably have to increase the price of your gig according to time, quality and the kind of work you get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;diversify&#34;&gt;Diversify&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fiverr alone can&amp;rsquo;t get you anything. Or for that case, &lt;em&gt;[insert freelancing platform] can&amp;rsquo;t get you anything.&lt;/em&gt; I say that because its really important that you create gigs on many different platforms, at the minimum at least do 2. This allows you to get a better feel of the freelancing market especially for your niche or category of work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you do this, you will find yourself finding new ways to optimising your gigs every now and then which is a good thing. This also includes creating multiple gigs for the same thing but with different content to see what works the best for you. &lt;em&gt;(specifically on Fiverr)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;response-time&#34;&gt;Response time&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Install mobile apps to get notifications whenever there is a inquery about your gig. Trust me it affects by a lot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, just put yourself in the buyer&amp;rsquo;s shows. See what you would look for in a seller and do those things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, if someone wants to convert their designs or current website to Hugo, check out my gig.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-MB&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Welp</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/welp/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/welp/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Umm so the vim journey was short lived. It was very very annoying when you have so many things going through your head but you are thinking about which keys will take you at the end of the line so you can delete a semicolon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;can&amp;rsquo;t exit vim&lt;/em&gt; memes are real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;anyways, so yeah. No more vim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-website&#34;&gt;🕸 website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There have been some updates on the website. The main one is that I have articles in Roman Urdu now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always wanted to do this but I thought that it was too much work for a niche audience and I don&amp;rsquo;t even have enough users from Pakistan to take advantage of it but I did it anyways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think its coming from the fact that when I wanted to know stuff, I didn&amp;rsquo;t see anything which was originated from Pakistan. &amp;amp;&amp;amp; even if I know knew something about IT/tech; they would just gatekeep it or say that &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;you are still a child to know all this&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; - Hello what?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think who I am right now is all because of Google and just the internet overall. People, personally have treated me and other people like me in a bad way and I kinda want to change that. Initially this was supposed to be a YouTube channel and that&amp;rsquo;s because I was doing YouTube at the time but now its this so why not have Urdu copy of articles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and yes roman Urdu because most people know roman Urdu more than Urdu Urdu and my primary target audience are teenagers/&amp;ldquo;GenZ&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it for today, I just wanted to talk about the roman Urdu thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Vim</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/vim/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/vim/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;updates&#34;&gt;Updates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So the website has been changed &amp;amp; I have applied adsense, hopefully they are kind this time around but who knows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website has been great and I have been updating things especially SEO things since the structure is quite different to what I was using before &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://github.com/526avijitgupta/gokarna&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;em&gt;GoKarna&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;upwork&#34;&gt;Upwork&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I have been using Twitter or X much more now and I follow this web developer, &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://twitter.com/yb_fedev&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Julia&lt;/a&gt;. She posted this thread about getting work on Upwork and it was kind of eye-opening despite by tries/experiences so I decided to try again &amp;amp;&amp;amp; following what Julia said in her thread:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;5 tips that helped me to get my first client on Upwork👇🏼&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Julia👩‍💻 (@yb_fedev) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/yb_fedev/status/1752610754702843977?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;January 31, 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async src=&#34;https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I am quite hopeful but lets see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;college&#34;&gt;College&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hate how slow things. I mean it makes sense because there are like 30 students and the teacher has to keep everyone together but if I can and am doing things quicker then either give me some other things to do or just let me off for the day but nope. I have to sit in that class staring at walls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my tutor did give me another assignment while others are doing &amp;ldquo;the old one&amp;rdquo; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; this assignment is about web develoment so thats great. &amp;amp;&amp;amp; it reminds me of how unorthodox my workflow is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;vim&#34;&gt;Vim&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was looking for something new to learn &amp;amp; I was watching &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://christitus.com&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Chris Titus&lt;/a&gt; using neovim so that&amp;rsquo;s what I am going to learn now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;first-impressions&#34;&gt;First impressions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting with neovim or vim is a bad idea. especially for me who doesn&amp;rsquo;t like creative processes like customising things and there is no point of learning something else just to customise this thing called vim. So for now I am using the Vim extension on vscode; I am planning to use this for at least a year or something before considering using neovim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This newsletter is being written using Vim + VsCode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-MB&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Big Brother</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/big-brother/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/big-brother/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a block. An imaginary but physical block. Can’t write, can’t work on the website, can’t work on hobbies, can’t do anything. Hopelessness. The decision to write every week might be to optimistic but I have written 3 articles per week so one shouldn’t be a problem. I don’t know. Things not working makes me think of destructive things to do which isn’t good of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-website&#34;&gt;The Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mansoorbarri.com/img/newsletter/2024/big-brother/website.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;screenshot of the new website&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this is what it looks like right now but the search doesn’t work still which is annoying. The developer is inactive and its been a week but still there is no reply. I have used this theme before, the search worked then &amp;amp;&amp;amp; I tried importing my content on that website but still the search doesn’t work so I don’t know what the issue is. Its frustrating. But its more frustrating when you make a theme but decide not to be active for its support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hepton&#34;&gt;Hepton&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been posting content but there is no change in impressions so I guess we wait. I am thinking of writing articles for Hepton but I don’t think I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this newsletter, I might just post tiny tiny newsletters just so I make something. Even now writing this reminds me of 10 other things I have to do so yuh. Like Ali Abdaal said,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;motivation is a myth. Trying to get yourself to feel like doing something useful is a fool’s errand. A 3-year old bases their day-to-day decisions on what they feel like doing. An intelligent student/adult recognises that feeling like doing something useful should have absolutely nothing to do with whether they actually do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>End Of 2023</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2023/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2023/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This year has been a productive one to say the least. I manage to achieve many goals and did many things; even those which were unplanned. But lets start from last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🚀 Progress&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is how last year&amp;rsquo;s goals went:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 3 times a week on mansoorbarri.com: I was able to post 3 times a week for majority of the year however because of G-Adsense, I had to remove around 10% of my posts because of their guidelines even though they didn&amp;rsquo;t approve me yet. Some articles went on hepton.uk &amp;amp; some went on my profile over on Medium.com. Towards the end of this year, I stopped doing everything so there were no articles since November.
Commit and contribute more on GitHub: This is where I have been successful. I was able to commit to my own projects a lot more but more importantly, I contributed to others&amp;rsquo; code like GoKarna (My website&amp;rsquo;s Hugo theme) &amp;amp; some of my friends&amp;rsquo;. I will try to continue this however it won&amp;rsquo;t be my main focus.
Improve my network: If I&amp;rsquo;m being honest with myself, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even try.
⚔ &amp;lsquo;24&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create memories
Focus on what&amp;rsquo;s on hand rather than think about the future
&amp;ldquo;Quality over quantity&amp;rdquo;
These are the goals for 2024, I want to be more to myself rather than just focus on work or other people &amp;amp;&amp;amp; maybe get out of the cycle of doing too much work and taking a long break because of burn out. Because I used to believe that burn out wouldn&amp;rsquo;t affect me but 2023 demonstrated how wrong I was.
​&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With quality over quantity, I am thinking of starting a weekly journal series on Medium till December &amp;lsquo;24 &amp;amp; post on my website only when I have something technical to share.
​&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🧺 Misc&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be turning 18 officially this year so I am thinking of starting to invest in crypto &amp;amp; stocks, for which I have already started to learn and study how things work. Hopefully that goes well. 🤞&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy New Year to you doe &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Prototype</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/prototype/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/prototype/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am thinking of just publishing one post every week and a newsletter on the website since 3 was okay but its too much and there are lack of ideas which suit the website&amp;rsquo;s theme. I am starting to experiment with this but also post things which blur the boundaries of the &amp;ldquo;website theme&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am thinking of posting some content on Medium too as I do get some traffic on it which is more than my website&amp;rsquo;s traffic especially for writeups which makes sense as Advent Of Cyber 2023 is 4 days away. The aim is to get the website enough traffic so G-Ads are compelled to accept the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, the list was something like this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 3 times a week on mansoorbarri.com
Commit and contribute more on GitHub
Improve my network
Most of these this is achieved but I think networking can still be improved. In 2024, I for real want to make things right rather than hand on them for ages &amp;amp; do them when there is nothing else to do (G-Ads staring from the shadows)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;G-Ads
Long run clients for Hepton
Improve network OR get a job
G-Ads
Google ads has been pain in the neck especially since I know everything is okay but I still get rejected &amp;amp; they don&amp;rsquo;t tell me what is actually wrong so its a slay. However, I am thinking about actually working on it either by asking on forums or asking someone IRL who has done this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepton
There are no expenses except the domain which isn&amp;rsquo;t that expensive too. ($3). The only issue is that I do want to do this like make it actually work; not just because of money but because its like a little child who needs time to grow and I&amp;rsquo;m a impatient bitch. Currently, I am working on a social media campaign and thinking about running ads - I have already spent around $100+ over ads and domain for Hepton which makes me think if this will even work?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Job
College annoys me because I have done almost everything they teach and sometimes they teach it wrong which is frustrating but I can&amp;rsquo;t leave either cos its worth it now. Afterwards, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I will have time or energy to do this plus its probably just helpful towards my career.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to give exams like CompTIA A+ which I need money for as well. sigh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Either way, If you can help with any of these things i.e. clients or Google adsense then please do contact. thankies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it doe &amp;lt;3
it&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Day Dreaming</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/day-dreaming/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/day-dreaming/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I was listening to Van Neistat and he was talking about how he has this habit of fixing things and just fixing every little thing for no apparent reason and he called it &amp;ldquo;Fantasy Fixing&amp;rdquo; and I kind of related to him &amp;amp; this idea of fixing fixing stuff just because its like a form of gratitude in one way or another. One difference is that he is more of a hands-on guy where he fixes like &amp;ldquo;real stuff&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;m more of a IT-fantasy fixing guy. I would see something off from like a UI point of view or just something and would fix it and projects being open-source make it a lot more doable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This struck me while I was looking at my Hugo theme and you know - thinking of things which could be better and my sister asked &amp;ldquo;Why are you staring at it?&amp;rdquo; which lead me to this rabbit hole and me discovering that I just find some sort of happiness or have a passion for &amp;ldquo;Fantasy Fixing&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This also correlates to how I want to restore a vintage bike or car because that&amp;rsquo;s FIXING fr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🔀 Menace&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a guess (like always) that Google doesn&amp;rsquo;t like how my site doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a search box thing even though it has around 300 pages and personally I want search too so I decided to actually make it. Turns out its harder than I thought so I just went with Google&amp;rsquo;s Programmable Search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;​
I make another branch on Git and do everything and it looked fine but I wanted to make it better and do some animations and stuff &amp;amp; I needed some time for it so I just left it there. After like a day or two, merging all the branches and deleting the ones I don&amp;rsquo;t want which turned out to be all of them; all of them. Still I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I will get the code for the search thing or not. &lt;em&gt;sigh&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out I deleted the repository with my Hugo Theme as well 😭&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tbh I don&amp;rsquo;t know when this happened but I contacted GitHub now so lets see what they say about this dumbbitch &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🔫 Adsense&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I applied Google Adsense again but they hate me. yes they do. &amp;amp; they said that I can&amp;rsquo;t re-apply till 20th November now because I applied to many times. - at this point, I think they should just tell me what&amp;rsquo;s wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I applied without adding search on the site so it might be that but I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I mean they do have &amp;ldquo;webmaster guidelines&amp;rdquo; as one of the reasons so it probably is but mehh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🧘 Posts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website has been pretty dry because I had no idea what to post plus I was sick for the first 3 days of the week which is 2/3 posts missed so I might as well not post any however, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to post next week too so like?!?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;let me know if you have any ideas though but other than that, thats it &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Icks and Observations</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/icks-and-observations/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/icks-and-observations/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this week has been a bit dry to be honest since there was nothing to do except just college and back home. Its half-term now so I’m free for a week or so. Somethings I want to achieve this week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;run Google ads for Hepton&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to at least one open-source project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;update assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;also, assignments, I got one of them back and I got 20/100 which is disgusting. I feel intellectually molested. but But BUT, I will update it and change some things around however I do think the teacher was a bit harsh on it since it just needs 2 things and then its fine so like 20? seems a bit too much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-ads&#34;&gt;🧮 Ads&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plan was to run ads on Instagram but you need Facebook account to put ads on Instagram like bruh wut? I mean it makes sense from a company’s POV but then stop banning people?!?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, the plan now is to try with Google. I have made a business profile which might help? I don’t know?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-observations&#34;&gt;👀 Observations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will have this section on every mail now because it just seems relevant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn long: i don’t know who needs this (i think everyone does) but ALWAYS TURN LONG. TURN FROM THE LONG WAY. especially around blind corners. I don’t want you to be 0.5cm away from your face. Tbh, just follow driving rules while walking as well. Please.
2FA: I find it so annoying that you have to press enter after typing your 2FA code. I like how GitHub does it; as soon as you enter the code, it just continues on rather than wait for you to press enter. please take this UX idea. ty
Issues: I got a GitHub issue with my Hugo theme &amp;amp; I get what people mean by not creating issues “the right way”. “It’s not working” doesn’t cut it. Say what you did, when did u experience it not working, what was the code, tell about your machine. Make this about you and not just “its not working.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-website&#34;&gt;🚧 Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I usually change the layout of my website every year. This year I don’t really have any complaints except the site not having search and I have tried adding it manually but its just not working. I talked about this with my friend and she says that she wants to give it a try - let’s wait &amp;amp; watch otherwise I will have to change and I don’t know which theme to use because nothing beats my site :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-wpm&#34;&gt;⌨ WPM&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reached 110 words per minute which took a while but happened, I have no evidence for it because I was doing it in college but I do have this picture where I got 108. Feels amazing but I don&amp;rsquo;t know where will this be useful lol - I mean it does help in productivity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-guide-of-the-week&#34;&gt;🗓 Guide of the week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;​How to automate your GitHub profile​&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think thats it for now &amp;lt;3 &amp;amp; also you can reply to this email to reply to the newsletter which I find just- 🤯&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Cyber War</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/cyber-war/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/cyber-war/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;baingen,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a good week for the website; there was a post every other day with guides as well as newsletters so it was a slay. College has been pretty boring too since I already know most of the stuff so I don&amp;rsquo;t even know what to do in lectures. tbh i&amp;rsquo;m just waiting for the programming/coding topic to start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-war&#34;&gt;⚠ War&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;we all know what has been happening past week. Cyber security wise, its been a mess, Sudan attacking Israel, Indians attacking Palestine, some attacking both sides. I doubt they are state-backed but defo hacktivists; I will link this video by Seytonic. He explains it well:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6zYloNKD-08&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://functions-js.convertkit.com/playbutton?play=%23324C85&amp;amp;accent=%23ffffff&amp;amp;thumbnailof=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D6zYloNKD-08&amp;amp;width=480&amp;amp;height=270&amp;amp;fit=contain&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;video preview&#34;
	
	
&gt;​&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;--hepton&#34;&gt;🗺  Hepton&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have created a bit of content to post as well as post as ads for impressions and just clients since Nextdoor isn&amp;rsquo;t that active and people require laymen and gutter-peeps more than IT guys tbh. Might just change careers 🤔&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, we are now on X as well or Twitter: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://twitter.com/@heptonuk&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://twitter.com/@heptonuk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the point is to get our name on as much platforms as possible &amp;amp; we are planning to play ads on Instagram too so lets see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;​&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;--guide-of-the-week&#34;&gt;🧭  Guide of the week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;​&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://mansoorbarri.com/guides/godot/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://mansoorbarri.com/guides/godot/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Come Back</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/come-back/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/come-back/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Halo again,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its been more than a week since I posted so the website is quite dry, I have some ideas for this week so this might just be a come back from being dry-asf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;--game-development&#34;&gt;🎮 | Game Development&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to try game development since I had this idea and wanted to try it before I regret and its no longer relevent. I won&amp;rsquo;t really say the idea of the game for obvious reasons however it was a multiplayer game which required me to develop an API i think which was just a big turn off to be honest. The experience just made me appriciate game devs a bit more as it requires a lot to develop a game let alone maintain it and bring updates which actually work and are interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;--c--apps&#34;&gt;👨‍💻 | C# &amp;amp; apps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am planning to learn C# by developing an app for Linux, it would be like an utility app but I don&amp;rsquo;t know how useful it will be since everything on Linux is quite nice by default. My prediction is that it will most likely be useful for beginners or admins who set up systems day-in &amp;amp; out and want a tool for quick setup; something like ninite 👀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it for now I guess &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Creative Block</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/creative-block/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/creative-block/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Been a while, I didn&amp;rsquo;t send anything to you or on the website because I fr don&amp;rsquo;t know what to post. At a point, I did have some ideas but my laziness did not write them down and of course I forgot. I am working on a couple of things which might be informative so there will be posts however the streak is broken now which is sad and I don&amp;rsquo;t plan to make it again. I think I might change to a post per week from next year and see how it goes but for now I don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am planning to make a game with my cousin however the block is still there and there are very confusing and contradictory information on the web. So possibly there will be documentation of that process here and technical tips and things like that, on the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;hepton&#34;&gt;Hepton&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepton is struggling on the side as well since there are no new clients and I was seriously thinking about marketing and then again I need a post which is interesting and engaging enough to market so its just- everything is at a stand still as of now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Assign-mint</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/assign-mint/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/assign-mint/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Ho Ho Ho,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started this instead of blog since I wanted to have something a bit more personal and not just something which is there on the internet for literally everyone. This is &amp;ldquo;public&amp;rdquo; but its like this close community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;college&#34;&gt;College&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since my sister did her uni before me, she found assignments pretty hard especially with similarity and just stuff which is supposed to be similar like stats, titles, questions. &amp;amp; this was because she left everything for the last minute, thats why I am trying to do everything before anyone else in the class and it worked so YAY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;shawty&#34;&gt;shawty&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This letter is a bit short because I wrote a proper one and lost it. Next week it is gonna be a proper one. You can also find archives/old letters at &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter&#34; &gt;/newsletter&lt;/a&gt; but a week later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Academia</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/academia/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/academia/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;update&#34;&gt;Update&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the last blog, adsense is still pending however I have planned a guide about adsense and what I used till now to get at least nearer to being accepted by Google. Will be live when I get accepted officially since I might use something new in the meanwhile.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;gcse&#34;&gt;GCSE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Got the expected grades however they increased the grade boundaries to pre-covid level even though this batch was in COVID in year 9 but slay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have applied for BTEC IT and got enrolled in the same which is gonna be fun hopefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mortgage-market&#34;&gt;Mortgage Market&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The website is fine but the apps are being a bit naughty. Google Playstore want API level 34 however we have 31 and I don&amp;rsquo;t know jack-shit about app development and can&amp;rsquo;t recompile apparently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apple renewal is right around the corner however they wanna sell the business and there is no buyer as of now since there is little to no revenue. Makes it a lot harder to manage a buyer while also doging store&amp;rsquo; fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Streamline</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/streamline/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/streamline/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;context&#34;&gt;Context&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Decided to post blogs weekly probably which would be a bit informal and just about how things are going and my plans with mansoorbarri.com as the normal &amp;ldquo;blogging&amp;rdquo; wouldn&amp;rsquo;t fit in articles, guides or write-ups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mentioning the categories reminds me of how there are just two categories now &lt;code&gt;Guides&lt;/code&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;code&gt;Blogs&lt;/code&gt; making it easier for the end-user to just navigate through stuff. Since the change, I will be posting write-ups on &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://medium.com/@mansoorbarri&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt; and the normal articles will be on the company website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;company&#34;&gt;Company&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This reminds me of the &amp;ldquo;company&amp;rdquo;; as of last year I wanted to make mansoorbarri.com a company which didn&amp;rsquo;t make sense after a while so I registered &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://hepton.uk&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;hepton.uk&lt;/a&gt; as a &amp;ldquo;pool&amp;rdquo; of freelancers which brings the overall cost of services lower and makes it easier for freelancers to work at hepton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently the &amp;ldquo;freelancers&amp;rdquo; are just friends &amp;amp; family since I know how they work and the quality of work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;current-situation&#34;&gt;Current Situation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;rn I am applying for Google Adsense to make mansoorbarri.com self-sufficient and focus on hepton.uk but it seems harder than I thought as I have been rejected 7 times since Jan 23. This is also why I have removed guides on hacking tools and write-ups as well as articles as they infringe with Google Adsense&amp;rsquo; policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;future&#34;&gt;Future&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think I will be posting more on blogs as there is a lot going on but can&amp;rsquo;t promise anything as things are changing a lot more and college will be starting on 5th too but we&amp;rsquo;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>End of 2020</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2020/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2020/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;goals-for-2022&#34;&gt;Goals for 2022&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Posting how-to guides on mansoor.cf everyday&lt;/strike&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Learning and growing in CyberSecurity &lt;/strike&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;making mansoorbarri.com a IT company&lt;/strike&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Getting a job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It started off really well at the beginning of this year, but as I got busier, it became a weekly thing, then monthly, and finally a seasonal thing where I would post 5 guides every 2-3 months. However, in the last quarter, I really expanded this into a polished product, which I did not expect at all. We had a hiccup in the middle when Freenom took away mansoor.cf, but we came back up and running within a day, which I&amp;rsquo;m very proud of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning has also been an experience as I expanded my TryHackMe profile and experimented with IT as much as I could, whether by learning coding languages or VM-ing the shit out of my laptop, but overall it&amp;rsquo;s been a good year in terms of learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting a job and establishing mansoor.cf as a business are inextricably linked. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get a job because of my age, but I polished this site to the point where two people wanted IT support from me, and this site and how documented my knowledge played a big part in that. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working with mortgagemarket.uk.com on penetration testing and hope to find more interesting and fulfilling jobs/gigs in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2023-goals&#34;&gt;2023 Goals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post 3 times a week on mansoorbarri.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commit and contribute more on GitHub&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve my network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2022 was a great year, but I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to 2023 to be even better in almost every aspect of life because I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from my mistakes (trust me, there were many) and learned, and 2023 may just be a year of significant growth. 🤞🏽&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
