<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Recap on Mansoor Barri</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/recap/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Recap on Mansoor Barri</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>Mansoor Barri</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mansoorbarri.com/tags/recap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>End of 2020</title>
        <link>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2020/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://mansoorbarri.com/newsletter/end-of-2020/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;goals-for-2022&#34;&gt;Goals for 2022&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Posting how-to guides on mansoor.cf everyday&lt;/strike&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Learning and growing in CyberSecurity &lt;/strike&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strike&gt;making mansoorbarri.com a IT company&lt;/strike&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Getting a job&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It started off really well at the beginning of this year, but as I got busier, it became a weekly thing, then monthly, and finally a seasonal thing where I would post 5 guides every 2-3 months. However, in the last quarter, I really expanded this into a polished product, which I did not expect at all. We had a hiccup in the middle when Freenom took away mansoor.cf, but we came back up and running within a day, which I&amp;rsquo;m very proud of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning has also been an experience as I expanded my TryHackMe profile and experimented with IT as much as I could, whether by learning coding languages or VM-ing the shit out of my laptop, but overall it&amp;rsquo;s been a good year in terms of learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting a job and establishing mansoor.cf as a business are inextricably linked. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get a job because of my age, but I polished this site to the point where two people wanted IT support from me, and this site and how documented my knowledge played a big part in that. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working with mortgagemarket.uk.com on penetration testing and hope to find more interesting and fulfilling jobs/gigs in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2023-goals&#34;&gt;2023 Goals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post 3 times a week on mansoorbarri.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commit and contribute more on GitHub&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve my network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2022 was a great year, but I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to 2023 to be even better in almost every aspect of life because I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from my mistakes (trust me, there were many) and learned, and 2023 may just be a year of significant growth. 🤞🏽&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it ✌🏽&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
