<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosting on Mansoor Barri</title>
    <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/hosting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hosting on Mansoor Barri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.mansoorbarri.com/tags/hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Hosting</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/web-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/web-hosting/</guid>
      <description>so hosting is a bit weird especially for websites:
some are over paying some are scams some are just perfect and it all comes down to your workflow and what do you wanna host.
Static sites Static sites are basically websites with just html, css &amp;amp; js. Nothing more, nothing less. You can host them in multiple ways but my prefered method is with Cloudflare Pages because of the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a Free SSL Certificate for Your GoDaddy Subdomain using SSL Generator</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/free-ssl-on-godaddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/free-ssl-on-godaddy/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites GoDaddy Windows Hosting: This guide assumes that you are using GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s Windows Hosting service to host your website. If you are using a different hosting provider or operating system, the steps may vary.
Step 1: Generate your SSL certificate Navigate to https://punchsalad.com/ssl-certificate-generator/ in your web browser. Enter your subdomain and email address, then click &amp;ldquo;Generate Certificate.&amp;rdquo; Follow the prompts to verify your ownership of the domain via DNS. This typically involves creating a TXT record in your DNS settings with a provided code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting Your Static Website for Free with GitHub: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.mansoorbarri.com/guides/hosting/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer There are many ways to host static website for free. In this guide we will use github as a hosting platform. Github can only host static websites*
Prerequisites Github account Code for your website Main Step 1: Click the &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; icon and click &amp;ldquo;New repository&amp;rdquo; Step 2: Set basic info Keep a name for your repository. Adding &amp;lsquo;.github.io&amp;quot; at the end of your repo name is important
Make sure &amp;ldquo;Add a README&amp;rdquo; file is checked</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
